[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Arnaldo] The only thing that Diego did
was be a good brother to me.
[Emilia] You're coming with me
to meet your grandmother.
I want Diego Torillo's head.
Oh! I have the perfect man for that.
The formidable Jaguar.
[Damian] You're facing a very
unpredictable enemy.
Red Dragon…
[Mercedes] And this is the gun
I'll be using on Camia and Lily
the moment you defy Red Dragon's orders.
[Emilia] You just said a few words
and left.
[Raul] You need to hide.
Because you're Red Dragon's next target.
I'm not afraid of her.
[Helena] I'm thankful that despite
your differences with my daughter,
we can still be friends.
[Lily] You're like my glamorous
mother that I never had.
Hello, Madam.
[Lily] Madam? Who were you talking to?
Are you working for my enemy?
Are you Mercedes Palacio?
[man] I'm sorry, ma'am,
but they ganged up on us.
[Helena] I hope nothing comes
between me and Arnaldo next time.
And you're right, Emilia.
Diego is a thorn.
So, if you don't do something
about it tonight,
then you are the biggest thorn
in this family!
[Natalie] I want to help Lily.
In her fight against the Ardientes.
[Jepoy] All right. If you say so.
[Mercedes] Weren't you tasked with
getting Diego Torillo's head?
Or should I just kill you
together with Camia and Lily?
[pensive music playing]
[dramatic music]
[upbeat music playing]
See you soon, Mercedes Palacio.
Are you hungry?
[Arnaldo] Diego… Oh, it's ready.
-Try this.
-Wow. That looks good.
You know how to cook.
Nanny Loring taught me.
Get some rice and try this.
-Okay. I'll try it.
-I'll give you some.
[Arnaldo] What about you?
-Go ahead.
-No. We should eat together.
Here's your plate. I'll get you some rice.
-All right.
-[chuckles]
It smells so good.
I've been wanting to try it.
[both chuckle]
-Can I have some rice?
-Here.
I'll get you some.
[soft piano music playing]
-Is this enough?
-That's fine.
Let's have a taste…
-Just eat up.
-of Nanny Loring's recipe.
-It's delicious.
-Like it?
It's great. Wait, do I
know how to cook too?
-[Diego] You?
-[Arnaldo] Yeah?
All you know how to do is eat.
-Really? Oh, well.
-[laughs]
[Arnaldo] Hold on. Based on the pictures,
it looked like you were the one
who liked to eat.
[Arnaldo laughs]
You were a bit chubby.
Well, I love a good roast.
Yeah, I can't blame you for that.
[both laughing]
[Arnaldo] But this is really good.
[Diego] Thank you, Arnaldo.
I'll teach you how to cook.
But before you do that,
teach me how to chop wood first.
I can't get it… [laughing]
-[Diego] You can do it.
-[laughs]
[Helena sighs]
Well, darling. I have to go.
Okay?
Bye, Mama.
Uh… Mama, don't worry,
our mission is underway.
Oh. That's good.
I knew I could count on you, Emilia.
And… Oh, gosh.
I'm so sorry for my outburst earlier.
I did it for your own good.
How can I make it up to you?
Um…
Let's have Lily Cruz killed.
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Mercedes] Well, it was
really fun talking with you.
Yeah. I had fun.
If you want, we can keep
going and have fun all night.
[man] Hmm… Interesting.
[upbeat music playing]
[both giggling]
Now, you go.
No.
What, Mama?!
How can we not do that?
She's the enemy here, Mama!
[sighs] Darling, now's
not the right time to kill Lily.
Wow, Mama.
You guys are on a first-name basis?
[sighs] Looks like you really
enjoyed your lunch with her.
Well, I must admit, she is a lovely girl.
But she's too simple for our taste.
You are far more beautiful
and fabulous than her.
Please, my darling,
don't worry about
the existence of Lily Cruz.
Okay? We'll take our time.
It's more fun that way. [chuckles]
-Bye, Mama.
-Bye.
[dramatic music playing]
[both laughing]
-What were you saying?
-Anyway, I have to go.
-No, no, no! Don't worry.
-Wait, I'll take care of that.
I got this. I can take care of this.
I'm all right.
-Are you sure? Let me help you.
-It's very late. You have to go.
I'm all right.
-I have to go.
-Thank you.
-See you tomorrow.
-Okay.
Take care.
Okay, Arnaldo.
[Diego] Good night.
Good night. [chuckles]
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music playing]
What are you doing here?
Say your prayers
because you're about to die.
[grunts]
[suspenseful music continues]
[groaning]
Take him.
[suspenseful music continues]
[sighs]
[Lily] Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[moans]
-[man] Hey, are you okay?
-[Lily] Sorry. Sorry.
-[man] Are you okay?
-[Lily giggling] Yes. I'm sorry.
[elevator opens]
[Lily] Sorry.
[chuckles]
[tense music playing]
[elevator dings]
[action music playing]
-Put him there.
-[Diego panting]
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to do this to you.
[suspenseful music]
Did Red Dragon order you to kill me?
Want do you want from me?!
[woman] You talk too much.
Jaguar, finish him off!
[suspenseful music continues]
[gunshots]
[Damian] You're here again, fake Jaguar?!
Let Diego go!
He has nothing to do with this!
[suspenseful music]
[Damian] You confuse me.
One moment, you're a criminal.
Now, you're a vigilante?
Let Diego go!
-[gunfire]
-[Raul groans]
-[woman groans]
-[gunfire continues]
Diego! Run!
[gunfire continues]
[Damian] Go after Diego!
I'll deal with that impostor!
[Raul panting]
[suspenseful music]
-[suspenseful music]
-[Diego panting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[heavy breathing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[both grunt]
[grunting]
Wait! What do you want from me?!
[woman] We're here to kill you!
[grunting]
[groaning]
-[Diego grunts]
-[woman groans]
[suspenseful music playing]
Did you really think it'd be that easy?
[woman] What are you waiting for, Jaguar?
-Kill him!
-I'm on it!
[gunshot]
Go on.
I said, leave!
Why are you stopping?! Search over there!
[suspenseful music swelling]
[Diego panting]
[Raul groans]
[Raul growls]
[Raul] Let Diego go!
He has nothing to do with this!
-[gunshot]
-[Raul groans]
-Diego, run!
-[gunfire]
[suspenseful music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
Dad?
You're the Jaguar?
[heavy breathing]
[slow instrumental playing]
[water pouring]
[muffled screams]
[Rufo] Diego, let's get out of here.
-[Rufo] Come on!
-[Diego] Who are you?
-We're Jaguar's men.
-Who's Jaguar?
You'll find out soon enough. Let's go.
I'm not going with you!
You really are stubborn. Jaguar was right.
[Diego] Wait! Who's Jaguar?!
[Diego] What do you want from me?
[Rufo] Given your situation,
you're the one who needs him.
He's going to help you run for governor.
[Diego] First of all, I don't trust anyone
who hides their face
and doesn't choose to talk.
[groaning]
[Raul] You need allies.
Someone on your side.
You need the protection of strong people.
Like Jaguar.
If he protects you,
you'll be ruling over Ardiente.
Hang on, Dad. Do you know Jaguar?
Why do you want me to side with him?
Are you working together?
[groans]
[panting]
[upbeat music playing]
[sprays]
[tense music playing]
[beeps]
[ominous music playing]
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful sting]
[error alert]
[slow instrumental playing]
[groans]
Where am I?
We're safe here.
Dad, tell me the truth.
Are you the Jaguar?
Yes.
I'm the Jaguar.
So that's why you helped set me free.
Listen to me, Diego.
I'm doing all this…
because it's the only way for me…
to protect you.
What about the scandals?
The gambling dens?
Were you behind all those?
Dad, I gave up everything for this town.
I even risked my own life.
But what did you do?
You're all the same.
You're no different from the Ardientes!
Say what you want, Diego.
Yes, I admit it.
But I only wear that mask…
to guarantee your safety,
to keep you from danger, to protect you.
And no matter what you say…
I never hurt you.
And now, I wore that mask again
to keep you safe from Red Dragon.
[slow instrumental playing]
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[keys clicking]
[error alert]
[suspenseful music playing]
[mechanical sound]
[keys clicking]
[beeps]
[tense music intensifies]
Mercedes Palacio and Helena Montoya.
[unsettling music playing]
[Raul] I wear that mask
to guarantee your safety,
to keep you from danger, to protect you.
I wore that mask again
to keep you safe from Red Dragon.
[Diego] This gold mask…
This is the key to Red Dragon's world.
[dramatic music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
-Oh.
-[man] Hi.
-Why did you come back?
-The key card.
I think I lost it.
[suspenseful music playing]
Excuse me.
[phone rings]
[Helena] Hello? Finally!
Mercedes, I can't reach you
on your cellphone.
I've been trying to call you.
You need to report to me ASAP.
Hello? Mercedes?
Can you hear me?
[Lily] I hear you loud and clear.
There's no mistaking it.
I know it's you.
You, Helena Montoya, are none
other than Red Dragon!
[suspenseful music]
Helena Montoya as Red Dragon.
[thumps]
And now, my enemy finally has a face.
[door slowly opens]
[suspenseful music continues]
[door closes]
[suspenseful sting]
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[tense music playing]
[groans]
[sighs]
Give me that.
[exhales]
[Helena] Mercedes.
Has Diego Torillo been dispatched?
Remember, it's my daughter's request.
[Mercedes sighs]
Still no update from the Dragon
Ladies who went after Diego.
But until now, they haven't
found him in the area.
That doesn't mean to say
that Diego's dead.
If you had only answered my call earlier…
you wouldn't have to report this to me.
You don't know?
Then tell me, who answered the phone?
Were you with someone?
You know I do not
tolerate daftness, Mercedes.
Tell me the truth.
Were you with someone?
Yes, Madam.
And I did not answer because I was wasted.
[laughing]
[gasps]
[Helena continues laughing]
They don't call me Red Dragon
for nothing, Mercedes!
And you, of all people, should know this!
I will burn you, and I will be
your personal hell…
especially if I find out
that you're lying to me
even with the most microscopic detail.
Or else, I'll be forced
to use this on you.
Now, you wouldn't want that,
Mercedes. Would you?
[ominous music]
If Helena is Red Dragon,
and she's Emilia's mother,
then her mother is a corrupt criminal.
[Camia chuckles]
Even a family of demons
can't hold a candle to them!
I don't care if Emilia really
is her daughter
or whoever she is.
What's important is that
I finally know who my enemy is.
That Red Dragon,
or Helena Montoya, better be ready.
Because I will ruin her
machinery, expose her secrets,
and destroy her the way
she destroyed my properties!
I will fight her in the way
only Lily Cruz can.
Red Dragon.
You better start hiding in your lair.
[dramatic music]
[foreboding music playing]
What are you watching?
Red Dragon is waiting for you.
[dramatic music playing]
-[Emilia] Hi, Mama.
-Emilia, darling.
Mama, an enemy out there is watching you.
They're waiting to destroy you.
I'm sure whoever was on the other line
plans to take you down.
Then, they should try me…
if they want to be reduced to ashes.
[sighs]
You're being paranoid, my dear.
Nothing has even happened yet.
Mama. You are in Ardiente.
Everyone else here
is backstabbing each other.
So, you have to watch your back, Mama.
That Mercedes. Are you sure
you can really trust her?
[sighs]
And Lily Cruz may be aware
that you are Red Dragon.
[laughs]
Emilia, sweetheart.
You really have an overactive imagination.
But we're not playing charades.
I have to be dead sure about my target…
before I waste my time on them.
Remember,
anyone who battles a dragon
should be ready to die in a blaze.
[dramatic music playing]
Is what Lily said about Helena Montoya
being Red Dragon true?
The Red Dragon that bombed her businesses?
-[Anna] Jepoy.
-She doesn't look like it.
I mean, she seems so kind.
[Anna] Yes, Mr. Pandoy, Miss Loring.
That's why we should be careful.
We shouldn't trust her or what
the media says about her.
[Jepoy] We have a powerful enemy.
She's as powerful as two Ardiente families
in their prime.
We might need another ally.
[Diego] What?
Helena Montoya is Red Dragon?
Yes.
That woman really is something.
She thought she could fool me?
She doesn't know how easily I use
my hands to play with fire
and how I'll play her for a sap.
We need to expose her.
Not yet, Diego.
I need stronger evidence.
Then she'll go to prison
and pay for what she did to Aguas Realty.
Did Red Dragon order you to kill me?
I've got an idea.
Whatever that is, Diego,
all right, I trust you.
[Diego] I'm confident…
that I can infiltrate
Red Dragon's hideout.
If you can, then I need to know
about Helena Montoya's other transactions,
as the one and only Red Dragon.
[tense music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Loring] There she is.
-Miss Loring, Mr. Pandoy.
-[Pandoy] Lily. Yeah.
-How is--Where's Diego?
Um, he had to take care
of something important.
But don't worry. He'll come home.
Should we go?
Uh… About your information on Red Dragon.
You know we're Team Lily all the way.
[Pandoy] That's true.
Thank you.
Now you know why I needed to be
at her medical mission.
Should we go in?
-[Pandoy] Sure.
-[Loring] Let's go.
[Pandoy] You go first.
[Helena] Thank you.
Good morning, dear residents of Ardiente.
This morning, we have a medical mission
for all kinds of illnesses that
you might be suffering from.
Please come in.
Oh, she's finally here! Miss Lily Cruz!
-[Lily] Helena.
-[applause]
[Helena] Let's give her
and her posse a round of applause.
Come here. Don't be shy. [laughs]
-Good morning to all of you.
-[Pandoy coughing]
Oh, oh, no. Do you have a cough?
-What?
-Come here. What's your name?
-Pandoy, ma'am.
-Come here, Mr. Pandoy.
You're coughing. Do you feel sick?
-Uh… No, ma'am.
-[Helena] But you're coughing.
How long has this been going on?
[Pandoy] Uh… Well, I get dizzy
when the sun is up, but--
Well, you're in luck because
we have a pulmonary expert.
Please see Dr. Santos. She'll help you.
Make sure this man gets
the attention that he needs.
Everybody, fall in line. Come on.
This is just the beginning, dear friends.
And also, to those with dental needs.
Next time, I'll bring
dentists here to you.
Remember: onward, Ardiente!
Huh?
Boring news.
Oh! Hi, Papa.
-Hi, Emilia.
-Do you need anything?
I so know you, Papa.
You're dying to ask me a favor.
What is it that you need?
Fine.
I want you to tell me
where I can find your mother.
Hmm…
I'm not gonna do that. I can't.
Yeah, right. Come on,
just give me her address.
It's not as if she's the queen
of the underworld.
Emilia, if you don't want
to give me her address,
then just please call her.
Papa, Mama doesn't want you anymore.
Please call her!
Okay.
[man] If you have any problems
just tell me.
-[phone ringing]
-Oh. Excuse me.
Hello, Emilia.
[Emilia] Hello, Mama.
Where are you?
I'm endearing myself
to the masses, darling.
Mama, you're not supposed to do that.
You should find the enemy.
Don't worry, Emilia.
I can handle things, okay?
Anyway, Papa's looking for you.
He said you were going to meet.
[laughs]
Well. Hmm. Tell him to wait tonight.
Okay? All right, I have to go.
Lily Cruz has her eye on me.
Lily Cruz? You're with her?
Yes. Okay then, I have to go.
Bye. Be a good girl.
Okay, Mama. You too.
[dramatic music]
She told you to wait.
But I won't. Excuse me, Papa.
She's with Lily Cruz?
[Camia] Okay. Please get the car ready.
-Okay, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Damian.
Are you not coming to the medical mission?
Helena Montoya is the one behind that.
Lily suspects she's a criminal, right?
Wouldn't it be too dangerous
for you there?
[sighs] If that's the case,
Lily needs me there with her.
Damian, she's my daughter.
Her enemy is my enemy too.
If she gets hurt, I will be there for her.
Because my daughter
and I share the same fate.
Are you sure you're not coming?
I'm feeling a little sick today.
What?
[slow instrumental playing]
Well, you aren't burning up.
No, I am. You just don't feel it.
Maybe I'm getting lovesick.
I need a hug to make me feel better.
Damian! [chuckles]
I'm not playing games here.
Wait, what if does get worse?
Do I need to stay and take care of you?
You don't have to. I can handle myself.
-You should go.
-Are you sure?
All right. But I'll get you
some medicine first.
I have to make sure
you take it before I go.
I think a kiss will do the trick.
Even just one.
[snickers]
You're so silly, Damian.
Well, I'll be going now.
Take care of yourself.
[Lily] Helena, my newfound friend!
Lily! [laughs]
People of Ardiente, Helena here
is my new friend.
You are so different from the Ardientes.
You deserve a round of applause
for everything you've been doing.
You are so kind, Helena.
And because of that,
I am more than willing to donate
and support your good cause.
Oh, thank you so much, Lily.
And I heard you've held, so many projects
to help the people too.
A good team-up with you would be perfect!
-Yes!
-[Helena laughing]
Miss Lily Cruz is
such a good person, isn't she?
[woman] Yes, ma'am. She's so kind.
Miss Lily Cruz is the one
who gave us back our land
when the Ardientes took it from us.
Just like you, Miss Helena,
Miss Lily has held a lot
of projects for us here.
[Danny] Lily and Helena working together?
Onward, Ardiente!
-[all] Onward, Ardiente!
-[Helena] Onward, Ardiente!
-[Danny] Onward, Ardiente!
-[all] Onward, Ardiente!
This is for each and every one of you.
[foreboding music playing]
[Lily] Just last week,
Miss Helena Montoya
came here to Poblacion Ardiente
and asked me to speak
in front of all of you
so I could be a part of her advocacy.
[applause]
And because we are only private citizens
who aren't affiliated
with any political parties,
Helena Montoya
and I will be working together
to push Poblacion Ardiente
to greater heights.
That's why Miss Helena Montoya
conducted a medical mission here today,
and she will also be giving
medical assistance
to other areas around Poblacion Ardiente.
Along with that,
my mother Camia Cruz and I
will be donating 5 million pesos
to erect another clinic here
in Poblacion Ardiente.
[applause]
[Helena laughs]
-[Emilia] Excuse me. Excuse me.
-[Helena] Thank you.
[Emilia] I'm going to donate
10 million pesos.
[dramatic music playing]
Hi, Mama.
I apologize. I think I misheard that.
Was that 10 million pesos?
Emilia, I didn't know
you were a magician now too.
Call me whatever you want,
but yes, I can do that,
so you can leave now.
The real partner of my mother
has arrived, and that's me.
[tense music playing]
So, did you guys have fun
with the medical mission?
[tense music playing]
I'm sure, you'll have even more fun now
because Emilia Ardiente-Torillo is here,
the only daughter of Helena Montoya.
[Lily] Your mother and I
are serious about this project.
Well, I'm serious
about this too, Lily Cruz.
You know, we should be discussing
about, um, first aid.
Like, about… snake bites?
You know, a lot of people here
pretend to be nice.
You don't know when they'll
just kill you and bite you
and poison you with their venom.
That's so scary. Ouch.
So, Mama,
you better be careful
with the people around you.
[laughs]
[sighs]
Thank you for the warning, Emilia.
Helena, now you know.
You need to be careful
around your own daughter.
You know, Helena, I got
to know you, and I liked you.
I felt our connection to help the people
of Poblacion Ardiente. But I'm very sorry.
Because I can't go on with this project
if your daughter, Emilia, meddles in.
I guess it'll be better if you two
work together on this project.
Again, I'm sorry.
Hey!
-[Emilia] Hold the mic!
-[Lily] Guards.
[tense music playing]
Lily, wait.
Lily, please.
[Lily exhales]
[ominous music]
Helena!
[metal clanking]
-[Lily] Are you okay?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. Yes.
-[Lily] Helena, what--
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Helena.
-Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
Are you sure? You might have an injury.
[action music playing]
Can I ask you a favor?
I want to call you Mama.
Baby girl.
[Mercedes] If you don't show up
to the operation later,
this bullet will lodge itself in
the head of your beloved Camia.
[Lily] Red Dragon
is making a shipment tonight.
[Diego] I'll sabotage their delivery.
[Lily] I have to find a way
to help Diego's plan succeed.
[woman] There's something
different about you.
[theme music playing]